Now we're going to finish the decoration, by filling in the traced outline of the image that we did.
The best thing to do is to continue using markers, because it works best on the plastic, and don't try to use any kind of paints, or any kind of thick markers that go on that might weigh the plastic down.
The best is to use just standard permanent markers.
It goes on great on the plastic.
What's good about this step is that it takes a while to do the image, obviously depending on what type of image you want to make, but it also is very helpful when doing a project, and you're on some type of time schedule.
So, this is a great part of the project that can be easily manipulated.
If you wanted the project to be drawn out over a couple hours, or break it up into a few days this is really the step that can help you do that, by giving them more opportunities to make some type of decoration on the kite.
If you want to make it a little quicker, what you can do is you can take the plastic yourself, and you can make the outline, and have it ready for them, so all they have to do is just come and fill in the colors.
So, this step is a key step in the kite making when you're organizing projects for kids, or anybody for that matter, and it helps you really stick to a type of time schedule that meets your needs.
Now obviously, the more colors you use the nicer the outcome will be, and also the nicer effect it will have once it's flying.
They'll actually be able to spot it, and see it a lot better.
So, now we've finished putting in the color on our image, and we can see what a big difference it makes.
So now I've shown you how to finish coloring your kite with permanent markers.